{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Gianluigi7.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sicuro",
            "failed": 11,
            "lastAsked": 1490376999.2599657,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sure\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 16
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "guastarsi",
            "failed": 11,
            "lastAsked": 1490376996.5568702,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to spoil, to go bad\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 16
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "parecchie volte",
            "failed": 10,
            "lastAsked": 1490377061.4711802,
            "question": "Given the definition \"several times\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 15
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sapore"
            ],
            "answer": "il sapore",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1490377041.275716,
            "question": "Given the definition \"taste\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 14
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "for that reason",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1490377056.879197,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"percio\"?",
            "tried": 14
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "saporito",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1490377006.5521915,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tasty, savoury\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "saggio",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1490377002.2479668,
            "question": "Given the definition \"wise\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a seconda della stagione",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1490377047.8671994,
            "question": "Given the definition \"depending on the season\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "taste",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1490377133.6081235,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il sapore\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la pesca",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1490377155.7805474,
            "question": "Given the definition \"peach\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dry, dried",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1490377085.554353,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"secco\"?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "correre",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1490377153.2447262,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to run\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il fruttivendolo",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1490377160.0914478,
            "question": "Given the definition \"fruit vendor\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to spoil",
                "to spoil, to go rotten"
            ],
            "answer": "to spoil, to go bad",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1490377078.4267323,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"guastarsi\"?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "percio",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1490377130.880878,
            "question": "Given the definition \"for that reason\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "richiedere",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1490377150.8851168,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to require, request\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la tavola",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1490377195.3674946,
            "question": "Given the definition \"table\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "rotondo",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1490377182.1918292,
            "question": "Given the definition \"round\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to request, require",
                "to request"
            ],
            "answer": "to require, request",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1490377175.3204339,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"richiedere\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "rettangolare",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1490377165.2129414,
            "question": "Given the definition \"rectangular\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "peach",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1490377204.9795713,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la pesca\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la pera",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1490377202.0198987,
            "question": "Given the definition \"pear\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "wise",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1490377191.8238845,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"saggio\"?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "rectangular",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1490377198.6597822,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"rettangolare\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ciotola"
            ],
            "answer": "la ciotola",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1490377215.0913339,
            "question": "Given the definition \"bowl\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tasty, savory"
            ],
            "answer": "tasty, savoury",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1490377259.5620117,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"saporito\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "anche",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1490377236.9267437,
            "question": "Given the definition \"also\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "stamattina",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1490377221.4317195,
            "question": "Given the definition \"this morning\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to know",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1490377240.1827629,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sapere\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "odiare",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1490377207.0358748,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to dislike, hate\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fresco",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1490377242.7108595,
            "question": "Given the definition \"fresh\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "zucchinis"
            ],
            "answer": "zucchini",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1490377218.2837093,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"le zucchine\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "several times",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1490377262.793942,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"parecchie volte\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "outdoor market",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1490377290.5215127,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il mercato\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "le zucchine",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1490377302.2647705,
            "question": "Given the definition \"zucchini\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il mercato",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1490377278.8621604,
            "question": "Given the definition \"outdoor market\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sure",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1490377304.0972302,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sicuro\"?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to run",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1490377280.9017005,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"correre\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "verita"
            ],
            "answer": "la verita",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1490377306.8007393,
            "question": "Given the definition \"truth\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ovale",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1490377292.321868,
            "question": "Given the definition \"oval\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "delicious",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1490377309.5769072,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"squisito\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fruit vendor",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1490377339.116302,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il fruttivendolo\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pear",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1490377311.5296462,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la pera\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "squisito",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1490377320.2130423,
            "question": "Given the definition \"delicious\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "secco",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1490377328.1633985,
            "question": "Given the definition \"dry, dried\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to hate, dislike",
                "to hate"
            ],
            "answer": "to dislike, hate",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1490377322.212983,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"odiare\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "i peperoni",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1490377342.9762316,
            "question": "Given the definition \"peppers\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "le banane",
                "banana"
            ],
            "answer": "la banana",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1490377325.780368,
            "question": "Given the definition \"banana\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "depending on the season",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1490377368.21173,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a seconda della stagione\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chiedere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1490377349.4401577,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to ask (for)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fresh",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1490377358.8241959,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fresco\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "cipolla"
            ],
            "answer": "la cipolla",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1490377356.9045334,
            "question": "Given the definition \"onion\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sapere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1490377346.640906,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to know\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "also",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1490377344.6405852,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"anche\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'arancia",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377361.1717305,
            "question": "Given the definition \"orange\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "this morning",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377352.1928895,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"stamattina\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "orange",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377372.3155866,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'arancia\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "truth",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377389.3117855,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la verita\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'uva",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377380.0275016,
            "question": "Given the definition \"grapes\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "oval",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377370.3636236,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ovale\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "i funghi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377374.7798898,
            "question": "Given the definition \"mushrooms\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "vegetable"
            ],
            "answer": "vegetables",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377386.8717287,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la verdura\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "mela"
            ],
            "answer": "la mela",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377391.206966,
            "question": "Given the definition \"apple\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "peppers",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377377.5547845,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"i peperoni\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "round",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377413.1464682,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"rotondo\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "banana",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377395.2231164,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la banana\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "mushrooms",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377416.0188978,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"i funghi\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "table",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377397.511366,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la tavola\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "grape"
            ],
            "answer": "grapes",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377406.1745973,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'uva\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "apple",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377400.3747132,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la mela\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "caldo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377411.1635463,
            "question": "Given the definition \"warm, hot\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "hot"
            ],
            "answer": "warm, hot",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377417.6827083,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"caldo\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bowl",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377425.4745536,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la ciotola\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to ask for",
                "to ask"
            ],
            "answer": "to ask (for)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377421.2025065,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"chiedere\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "onion",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377423.2588472,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la cipolla\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "verdura"
            ],
            "answer": "la verdura",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1490377427.9469419,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vegetables\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        }
    ]
}